Guide to the Peter Burton papers circa 1960-2008.
Burton, Peter
- Series IV. Personal Reference Collection
  - Alphabetical by Name
    - Caleb Carr (Box 8, Folder 109)
    - Dina Carroll (Box 8, Folder 110)
    - Michael Carson (Box 8, Folder 111)
    - Simon Carter (Box 8, Folder 112)
    - Roger Casement (Box 8, Folder 113)
    - Michael Cashman (Box 8, Folder 114)
    - David Cassidy (Box 8, Folder 115)
    - caVa caVa (Box 8, Folder 116)
    - George Chakiris (Box 8, Folder 117)
    - Michael Chabon (Box 8, Folder 118)
    - Charleston (Box 8, Folder 119)
    - Cher (Box 8, Folder 120)
    - Children's Television (Gay Imaging) (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Agatha Christie (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Anne Clarke (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Tim Clarke (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Tom Clarkson (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - A Class Apart (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Claudia (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Phill Clegg (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Montgomery Clift (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Clint Flick (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Eddie Cochran (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Coctean Twins (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Desmond F. T. Coke (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Nat "King" Cole (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Colette (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Jackie Collins (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - The Colourfield (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Comics (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Communards (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Bryan Connon (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Jasper Conran (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - John Conteh with Spandau Ballet (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Barbara Cook (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Gary COoper (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Stewart Copeland (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - John Cornelius (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Simon Corrisan (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Alma Cosan (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - John Cougar (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Johnny Cougar, Oversize (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Noel Coward (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Noel Coward and Switzerland (Photographs) (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Quentin Crisp (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Kim Crisswell (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Andy Crock (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Crocodile Tears (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Tom Cruise (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Nancy Cunard (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - The Cure (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Curiosity Killed the Cat (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Roland Curram (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Tony Curtis (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Peter Cushing (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - People "D" (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Roger Daltry (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Bobby Darin (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Elizabeth David (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Michael Davidson (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Terence Davies (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Bette Davis (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Daniel Day-Lewis (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Dead Kennedys (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Dead Or Alive (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Hazell Dean (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - James Dean (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Vikki de Lambray (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Michael De-La-Hoy (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Judi Dench (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Chris Denning (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Johnny Depp (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Peter de Rome (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Leonardo DiCaprio (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Kay Dick (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Kay Dick (New Dictionary of National Biography) (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Charles Dickens (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Dislocation Dance (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Marlene Dietrich (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Reginald Dixon (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Dollimore and Sinfield (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Anton Dolin with Marie Rambert (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Philip Dooley-Scott (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Jason Donovan (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Dorian Opera (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - Diana Dors (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Dorson and Gray (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Margaret Drabble (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - The Dream Academy (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Peter Dudley (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Stephen Tintin Duffy (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Ian Dury (Box 9, Folder 79)
    - Sheena Easton (Box 9, Folder 80)
    - EFUA (Box 9, Folder 81)
    - Elizabeth, Queen, the Queen Mother (Box 9, Folder 82)
    - Bret Easton Ellis (Box 9, Folder 83)
    - David Essex (Box 9, Folder 84)
    - Everything But The Girl (Box 9, Folder 85)
    - E'Van Everly (Box 9, Folder 86)
    - People "F" (Box 9, Folder 87)
    - The Fabulous Thunderbirds (Box 9, Folder 88)
    - Fad Gadget (Box 9, Folder 89)
    - Betty Fade (Box 9, Folder 90)
    - Douglas Fairbanks Jr. (Box 9, Folder 91)
    - Marianne Faithful (Box 9, Folder 92)
    - Simon Fanshawe (Box 9, Folder 93)
    - Fantastic Something (Box 9, Folder 94)
    - Farewell (Box 9, Folder 95)
    - Peter Farmer (Box 9, Folder 96)
    - Robert Farrar (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - Kathleen Farrell (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - Fascinating Aida (Box 9, Folder 99)
    - The Fast (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - Alice Faye (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - Federico Fellini (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - Felt (Box 9, Folder 103)
    - Rick Ferreiira (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - Bryan Ferry (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - Fenella Fielding (Box 9, Folder 106)
    - Gracie Fields (Box 9, Folder 107)
    - W. C. Fields (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - Ralph Fiennes (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - 52nd Street (Box 9, Folder 110)
    - Graham Fitkin (Box 9, Folder 111)
    - Fine Young Cannibals (Box 9, Folder 112)
    - Albert Finney (Box 9, Folder 113)
    - Tim Flavin (Box 9, Folder 114)
    - Flesh For Lulu (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - Floyd (Box 9, Folder 116)
    - Errol Flynn (Box 9, Folder 117)
    - Jane Fonda (Box 9, Folder 118)
    - Charles Henri Ford (Box 9, Folder 119)
    - Foreigner (Box 9, Folder 120)
    - 400 Blows (Box 9, Folder 121)
    - Peter Frampton/The Herd (Box 9, Folder 122)
    - Connie Francis (Box 9, Folder 123)
    - Frankie Goes To Hollywood (Box 9, Folder 124)
    - Aretha Franklin (Box 9, Folder 125)
    - Gillian Freeman/Edward Thorpe (Box 9, Folder 126)
    - Fun Boy Three (Box 9, Folder 127)
    - Billy Fury (Box 9, Folder 128)
    - People "G" (Box 9, Folder 129)
    - Christopher Gable (Box 9, Folder 130)
    - Diamanda Galas (Box 9, Folder 131)
    - Patrick Gale (Box 9, Folder 132)
    - Garbo (Box 9, Folder 133)
    - Kenny Gardener (Box 9, Folder 134)
    - James Gardiner (Box 9, Folder 135)
    - Judy Garland (Box 9, Folder 136)
    - Jane Gaskell (Box 9, Folder 137)
    - Jean Paul Gaultier (Box 9, Folder 138)
    - Gay and Lesbian Biography (Box 9, Folder 139)
    - Gay Publishing (Box 9, Folder 140)
    - Gay Writing and Publishing in the 1970s (R. F. Hall Lecture) (Box 9, Folder 141)
    - Genet (Box 9, Folder 142)
    - Richard Gere (Box 9, Folder 143)
    - George Gershwin (Box 9, Folder 144)
    - Gerty (Box 9, Folder 145)
    - Audre Gide (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - John Gilbert (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - W. Stephen Gilbert (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - John Gilegud (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Glasgow (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Go West (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Derek Goldby (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Golden Girls (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - June Goodfield (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - General Gordon (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Juan Gautisolo (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Lew Grade (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Gloria Grahame (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Julia Grant (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Dolores Gray (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Stephen Gray and Philip Bliss (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Larry Grayson (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Julian Green (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Thom Gunn (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - People "H" (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Nina Hagen (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Jonathan Hales (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Adelaide Hall (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Radclyffe Hall (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Gerald Hamilton (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Irene Handl (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Hanoi Rocks (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Joseph Hansen (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Gilbert Harding (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Thomas Hardy (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Roy Harper (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - L. P. Hartley (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - P. P. Hartnett (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Ian Harvey (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Steven Harwood (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - The Hassles (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Andrew Heard (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Heaven 17 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Heebeegeebees (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Robert Helpmann (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Ernest Hemmingway (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Henry VIII (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - James Herbert (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Kir Hasketh Harvey (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Charlton Heston (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Jack Hewit (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Patricia Highsmith (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Lonnie Hill (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Myra Hindley (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - David Hockney (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Andrew Hodges (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Matthew Hodson (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Merlin Holland (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Tony Holland (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Andrew Holleran (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Billie Holiday (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Jimmy Holiday (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Alan Hollinghurst (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Homoerotica (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Homophobia (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Hot Chocolate (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - A. E. Housman (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - The Housemartins (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Rock Hudson (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Paul Hull (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Human League (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Rita Hunter (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Eddy Huntington (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - People "I" (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Ibiza, October 1982 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Billy Idol (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - The Insinuendos (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - In The Nursery (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - INXS (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Christopher Isherwood (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Eddie Izzard (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - People "J" (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Tha Jam (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Edward James (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Chas Jankel (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - Jannot and Voulzey (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - Derek Jarman (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - Bernard Jay (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - Jenson-Morrow (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - Joan of Arc (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Jobriath (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - Elton John (Box 10, Folder 87)
    - Adam Johnson (Box 10, Folder 88)
    - Tony Johnson and William Nicholl (Box 10, Folder 89)
    - Aled Jones (Box 10, Folder 90)
    - Grace Jones (Box 10, Folder 91)
    - Howard Jones (Box 10, Folder 92)
    - Russell Celyn Jones (Box 10, Folder 93)
    - People "K" (Box 10, Folder 94)
    - Lila Kedrova (Box 10, Folder 95)
    - George, Duke of Kent and Marina, Dutchess of Kent (Box 10, Folder 96)
    - John Maynard Keynes (Box 10, Folder 97)
    - Kris Kirk (Box 10, Folder 98)
    - Maggie Kirkpatrick (Box 10, Folder 99)
    - Pat Kirkwood (Box 10, Folder 100)
    - C. H. B. Kitchin (Box 10, Folder 101)
    - David Knopfler (Box 10, Folder 102)
    - Kodo Drummers (Box 10, Folder 103)
    - Larry Kramer (Box 10, Folder 104)
    - Hanif Kureishi (Box 10, Folder 105)
    - People "L" (Box 10, Folder 106)
    - Charles Lamb (Box 10, Folder 107)
    - Constant Lambert (Box 10, Folder 108)
    - Gavin Lambert (Box 10, Folder 109)
    - LaTour (Box 10, Folder 110)
    - Charles Jaughton (Box 10, Folder 111)
    - Jude Law (Box 10, Folder 112)
    - T. E. Lawrence (Box 10, Folder 113)
    - David Leavitt (Box 10, Folder 114)
    - Heath Ledger (Box 10, Folder 115)
    - Led Zepplin (Box 10, Folder 116)
    - Harper Lee (Box 10, Folder 117)
    - Peggy Lee (Box 10, Folder 118)
    - Thomas Leer (Box 10, Folder 119)
    - John Lehmann (Box 10, Folder 120)
    - Vivien Leigh (Box 10, Folder 121)
    - Denis Lemon (Box 10, Folder 122)
    - Ute Lemper (Box 10, Folder 123)
    - John Lennon (Box 10, Folder 124)
    - Annie Lennox (Box 10, Folder 125)
    - Les Negresses Vertes (Box 10, Folder 126)
    - Level 42 (Box 10, Folder 127)
    - Ian Levine (Box 10, Folder 128)
    - Stephen Brimson Lewis (Box 10, Folder 129)
    - Serge Lifar (Box 10, Folder 130)
    - Limahl (Box 10, Folder 131)
    - Lindistarne (Box 10, Folder 132)
    - Verna Lindt (Box 10, Folder 133)
    - Little Richard (Box 10, Folder 134)
    - Maureen Lipman (Box 10, Folder 135)
    - Lip Service (Box 10, Folder 136)
    - Lip, Stick and Promise (Box 10, Folder 137)
    - "Gary London"/Gerry Collins (Box 10, Folder 138)
    - Julie London (Box 10, Folder 139)
    - Federico Garcia Lorca (Box 10, Folder 140)
    - Simon Lovat (Box 10, Folder 141)
    - James Blair Lovell (Box 10, Folder 142)
    - Michael Lowrie (Box 10, Folder 143)
    - Ian Lucas (Box 10, Folder 144)
    - Ludus (Box 10, Folder 145)
    - Lorna Luft (Box 10, Folder 146)
    - Joanna Lumley (Box 10, Folder 147)
    - Lohn Lydon (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - Kenny Lynch (Box 10, Folder 149)
    - Rita Lynch (Box 10, Folder 150)
    - James Lyons (Box 10, Folder 151)
    - People "M" (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Shena MacKay (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Shirley MacLaine (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Madonna (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Sean Maguire (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - David Malouff (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Manfred Mann (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - The Manhattan Transfer (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Manic Street Preachers (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Man to Man (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Mantronix (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Robert Mapplethorpe (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - The March Violets (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Marky Mark (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Bob Marley (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Steve Martland (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Brian Masters (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Sean Mathias (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Johnny Mathis (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Armistead Maupin (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Paul McCartney (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Jimmy McCulloch (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Joe McFadden (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Ewan McGregor (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Melon (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Memorabilia (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Micro Disney (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Bette Middler (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Arthur Miller (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Freddie Mills (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Billy Milton (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Joni Mitchell (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Julian Mitchell (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Marilyn Monroe (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Gary Moore (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Jeanne Moreau (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Ottoline Morrell (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Morrissey (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Jim Morrison (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Carl Morse (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Alison Moyet (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Marcia Muller (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Iris Murdoch (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Gerald Murphy (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - People "N" (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Naked Eyes (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Brendan Nash (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Nettle and Markham (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Byron Newman (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - New York Dolls (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - New York Gay Men's Chorus (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Jack Nicholson (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Klaus Nomi (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Norman (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Ivor Novello (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Gary Numan (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Raul Nunez (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Tommy Nutter (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - People "O" (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Sinead O'Connor (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Erwin Olaf (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Eric Oliver (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Paul Oremland (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Joe Orton (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Milo O'Shea (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - Christopher Osborn (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - Charles Osborne (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - John Osborne (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - Oscar Wilde Society (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - Philip Osment (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - Out In The Workplace (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - Mark Ovendon (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - Wilfred Owen (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - People "P" (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - Michael Paine (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - Pam's Birthday Book, Oversize (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Molly Parkin (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - James Parrish (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - Guy Pearce (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - Dale Peck (Box 11, Folder 79)
    - Luke Perry (Box 11, Folder 80)
    - Pat Phoenix (Box 11, Folder 81)
    - Physique Pictorial (Box 11, Folder 82)
    - The Best of Edith Piaf (Box 11, Folder 83)
    - Felice Picano (Box 11, Folder 84)
    - Pierre et Gilles (Box 11, Folder 85)
    - Pink Industry (Box 11, Folder 86)
    - Pin-Ups (Pride) (Box 11, Folder 87)
    - Brad Pitt (Box 11, Folder 88)
    - David Planke (Box 11, Folder 89)
    - The Pogues (Box 11, Folder 90)
    - The Police (Box 11, Folder 91)
    - Su Pollard and David Keogh (Box 11, Folder 92)
    - Pookah Makes 3 (Box 11, Folder 93)
    - Michael Portillo "Comes Out" (Box 11, Folder 94)
    - John Preston (Box 11, Folder 95)
    - David Price (Box 11, Folder 96)
    - Maxi Priest (Box 11, Folder 97)
    - P. J. Proby (Box 11, Folder 98)
    - People "Q" (Box 11, Folder 99)
    - Queen (Box 11, Folder 100)
    - People "R" (Box 11, Folder 101)
    - Marsha Raven (Box 11, Folder 102)
    - Simon Raven (Box 11, Folder 103)
    - David Rawley (Box 11, Folder 104)
    - Jimmy Ray (Box 11, Folder 105)
    - Raymonde (and James Maker) (Box 11, Folder 106)
    - Claire Rayner (Box 11, Folder 107)
    - Lloyd Recqord (Box 11, Folder 108)
    - Sharron Redd (Box 11, Folder 109)
    - Corin Redgrave (Box 11, Folder 110)
    - Vanessa Redgrave (Box 11, Folder 111)
    - Red Hot Chilli Peppers (Box 11, Folder 112)
    - Lou Reed (Box 11, Folder 113)
    - David Rees 1 (Box 11, Folder 114)
    - David Rees 2 (Box 11, Folder 115)
    - David Rees 3 (Box 11, Folder 116)
    - Robert Reese (Box 11, Folder 117)
    - Keanu Reeves (Box 11, Folder 118)
    - Joan Regan (Box 11, Folder 119)
    - Regine (Box 11, Folder 120)
    - Ruth Rendell (Box 11, Folder 121)
    - Debbie Reynolds (Box 11, Folder 122)
    - Cecil Rhodes (Box 11, Folder 123)
    - Cliff Richard (Box 11, Folder 124)
    - Wendy Richard (Box 11, Folder 125)
    - Richard II (Box 11, Folder 126)
    - Tony Richardson (Box 11, Folder 127)
    - Philip Ridley (Box 11, Folder 128)
    - Joan Rivers (Box 11, Folder 129)
    - Julie Roberts (Box 11, Folder 130)
    - Robin (Box 11, Folder 131)
    - Toby Robin (Box 11, Folder 132)
    - Peter Robins (Box 11, Folder 133)
    - Tom Robinson (Box 11, Folder 134)
    - Chris Robison (Box 11, Folder 135)
    - Bunny Roger (Box 11, Folder 136)
    - Kenny Rogers (Box 11, Folder 137)
    - Frederick Rolfe (Box 11, Folder 138)
    - Rolling Stones and Jagger (Box 11, Folder 139)
    - Frank Ronan (Box 11, Folder 140)
    - Mickey Rooney (Box 11, Folder 141)
    - Jerry Rosco (Box 11, Folder 142)
    - Diana Ross (Box 11, Folder 143)
    - Jim Roth (Box 11, Folder 144)
    - Johnny Rotten (Box 11, Folder 145)
    - Dave Royal (Box 11, Folder 146)
    - Rubyfruit (Box 11, Folder 147)
    - Run DMC (Box 11, Folder 148)
    - James Rushton (Box 11, Folder 149)
    - Jane Russell (Box 11, Folder 150)
    - People "S" (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Sade (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Ryuichi Sakamoto (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Philip Salon (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Sandra (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Tom Sargant (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Siegfried Sassoon (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - S. A. W. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Dorothy L. Sayers (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Richard Scanes (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Dick Scalan (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Joan Schenkar (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Greta Schiller (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Lawrence Schimel (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Arnold Schwarzenegger (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Sense (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - The Shadows (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Helen Shapiro (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Aiden Shaw (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Pete Shelley (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Martin Sherman (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Ned Sherrin (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Randy Shilts (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Bill Short (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Michelangelo Signorile (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Paul Simon (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Simply Red (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Frank Sinatra (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Edith Sitwell (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Christian Slater (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Wayne Sleep (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Small Faces (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Bessie Smith (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Chris Smith (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Paul Smith (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - The Smiths (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Soft Cell (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Jimmy Somerville (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - The Sound (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Spear of Destiny (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Colin Spencer (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Stephen Spender (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Victor Spinetti (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Dusty Springfield (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Rick Springfield (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Bruce Springsteen (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Duncan Sprott (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Squeeze (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Phillip James Squires (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - John D. Stamford (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Jo Stafford (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Eric Stanton (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Jermaine Stewart (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Rod Stewart & the Faces (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Rod Stewart & the Faces Programs, Oversize (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Sting (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Luke Stoneham (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Lytton Stratchey (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Steve Strange (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Strawberry Switchblade (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Barbra Streisand (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - The Style Council (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Donna Summer (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Penny Summer (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - Michael Sundin (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Rosemary Sutchiff (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Colin Swift (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Steve Swindells (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - Swinging Blue Jeans (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Sylvester (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - David Sylvian (Box 12, Folder 70)
    - People "T" (Box 12, Folder 71)
    - Taffy (Box 12, Folder 72)
    - Talk Talk (Box 12, Folder 73)
    - Talking Heads (Box 12, Folder 74)
    - Tasty Tim (Box 12, Folder 75)
    - Peter Tatchell (Box 12, Folder 76)
    - Elizabeth Taylor (Box 12, Folder 77)
    - Tears for Fears (Box 12, Folder 78)
    - Kiri Te Kanawa (Box 12, Folder 79)
    - 10cc (Box 12, Folder 80)
    - Ten City (Box 12, Folder 81)
    - Judy Tenuta (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - Helen Terry (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - Margaret Thatcher (Box 12, Folder 84)
    - Thieves (Box 12, Folder 85)
    - Thin Ice (Box 12, Folder 86)
    - Michael Thornton (Box 12, Folder 87)
    - Jack Tinker (Box 12, Folder 88)
    - Michael Tippitt (Box 12, Folder 89)
    - Blair Todd (Box 12, Folder 90)
    - Tongue Man (Box 12, Folder 91)
    - George Tooker (Box 12, Folder 92)
    - Vaughan Toulous (Box 12, Folder 93)
    - Pete Townshend (Box 12, Folder 94)
    - John Christopher Travers (Box 12, Folder 95)
    - Michel Tremblay (Box 12, Folder 96)
    - Trouble and Strife (Box 12, Folder 97)
    - Antony Tudor (Box 12, Folder 98)
    - Dikran Tulaine (Box 12, Folder 99)
    - Frank Tuohy (Box 12, Folder 100)
    - Thompson Twins (Box 12, Folder 101)
    - Two Nice Girls (Box 12, Folder 102)
    - People "U" (Box 12, Folder 103)
    - Fred Urquhart (Box 12, Folder 104)
    - People "V" (Box 12, Folder 105)
    - Gus Van Sant (Box 12, Folder 106)
    - Bobby Vee (Box 12, Folder 107)
    - Tim Vincent (Box 12, Folder 108)
    - People "W" (Box 12, Folder 109)
    - W. A. H (Box 12, Folder 110)
    - Rufus Wainwright (Box 12, Folder 111)
    - Larry Waites (Box 12, Folder 112)
    - Tom Waits (Box 12, Folder 113)
    - Tom Wakefield (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - Andy Warhol (Box 12, Folder 115)
    - Patricia Nell Warren (Box 12, Folder 116)
    - Tony Warren (Box 12, Folder 117)
    - Watusi Bros. (Box 12, Folder 118)
    - Elizabeth Welch (Box 12, Folder 119)
    - Peter Wells (Box 12, Folder 120)
    - Nick Wesley (Box 12, Folder 121)
    - Fred and Rosemary West (Box 12, Folder 122)
    - David Western (Box 12, Folder 123)
    - Jeff Western (Box 12, Folder 124)
    - WHAM (Box 12, Folder 125)
    - Edmund White (Box 12, Folder 126)
    - Patrick White (Box 12, Folder 127)
    - White & Torch (Box 12, Folder 128)
    - Peter Wildeblood (Box 12, Folder 129)
    - William the Conqueror (Box 12, Folder 130)